Cracked pavement and static on your morning screen Dead eyes behind the podium, parading every scene Shuffling their papers, but the ink is running thin Hope gets buried while the pandering begins Zombie commissar, take their marching orders high Never mind the bases, won't just shuffle and glide Voting red or blue, but they never wonder why
Brains are not a five, it's never hear our cries.
Hey, oh, brace the sin.
Lines drawn and sent, no matter what the people need Constituents ignored, as the lobby books the feed A hand up, a hand out, they're trading paper skin Plaster on their grins, now the walking dead begin We're shouting at their doors But their minds are locked up tight
A stampede of empty suits, dawn of the party like tonight.
Zombie congressmen take their munchie on a side, never mind good basis, one just shuffle and goodbye.
Voting ran afloat, but they never wonder why.
Brainjawn on a pilot, never hear our cries.
Ayo, bridge the sail.
Warren's Blair warnings as the brains go out to lunch.
Another round of chaos served up with a punch.
Truth DJs in silence while they're locked inside the dome.
We're still screaming loud, but getting set straight home.
Zombie congressmen take their marching orders high.
Never mind the faces, we're just shuffle and comply.
Voting ran a blue, but they never wonder why.
Brains are not a pilot, never hear our cries